question_data = [
    {"category": "Science & Nature", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy",
     "question": "Igneous rocks are formed by excessive heat and pressure.", "correct_answer": "False",
     "incorrect_answers": ["True"]}, {"category": "Entertainment: Film", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy",
                                      "question": "The movie ;The Nightmare before Christmas; was all done with physical objects.",
                                      "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
    {"category": "Entertainment: Film", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy",
     "question": "Leonardo DiCaprio won an Oscar for Best Actor in 2004s ;The Aviator;.",
     "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]},
    {"category": "Geography", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy",
     "question": "The Republic of Malta is the smallest microstate worldwide.", "correct_answer": "False",
     "incorrect_answers": ["True"]}, {"category": "Science: Computers", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy",
                                      "question": "Pointers were not used in the original C programming language; they were added later on in C++.",
                                      "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]},
    {"category": "Geography", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy",
     "question": "There is a city called Rome in every continent on Earth.", "correct_answer": "False",
     "incorrect_answers": ["True"]}, {"category": "Geography", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy",
                                      "question": "Alaska is the largest state in the United States.",
                                      "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
    {"category": "General Knowledge", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy",
     "question": "Nutella is produced by the German company Ferrero.", "correct_answer": "False",
     "incorrect_answers": ["True"]}, {"category": "Politics", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy",
                                      "question": "In 2016, the United Kingdom voted to stay in the EU.",
                                      "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]},
    {"category": "Entertainment: Video Games", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy",
     "question": "Faust is a playable character in ;Guilty Gear Xrd Revelator;.", "correct_answer": "True",
     "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}, {"category": "Science: Computers", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy",
                                       "question": "RAM stands for Random Access Memory.", "correct_answer": "True",
                                       "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
    {"category": "Science: Gadgets", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy",
     "question": "The communication protocol NFC stands for Near-Field Control.", "correct_answer": "False",
     "incorrect_answers": ["True"]}, {"category": "Entertainment: Video Games", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy",
                                      "question": "Tetris is the #1 best-selling video game of all-time.",
                                      "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]},
    {"category": "Mythology", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy",
     "question": "According to Greek Mythology, Zeus can control lightning.", "correct_answer": "True",
     "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}, {"category": "Politics", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy",
                                       "question": "Russia passed a law in 2013 which outlaws telling children that homosexuals exist.",
                                       "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
    {"category": "Entertainment: Video Games", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy",
     "question": "The ultimate phrase used by Pharah from Overwatch is: ;Justice rains from above!;",
     "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
    {"category": "Entertainment: Video Games", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy",
     "question": "The 2005 video game ;Call of Duty 2: Big Red One; is not available on PC.",
     "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
    {"category": "Entertainment: Film", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy",
     "question": "Samuel L. Jackson had the words, Bad Motherf*cker in-scripted on his lightsaber during the filming of Star Wars.",
     "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
    {"category": "Vehicles", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy",
     "question": "The full English name of the car manufacturer BMW is Bavarian Motor Works", "correct_answer": "True",
     "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
    {"category": "Animals", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy", "question": "Rabbits are rodents.",
     "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]},
    {"category": "Entertainment: Music", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy",
     "question": "The alternative rock band, They Might Be Giants, released their album Flood in 1990. ",
     "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
    {"category": "Entertainment: Board Games", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy",
     "question": "There is a Donald Trump Board Game, which was made in 1989.", "correct_answer": "True",
     "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}, {"category": "Entertainment: Comics", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy",
                                       "question": "The ;Pepe; meme originated from a comic drawn by Matt Furie called ;Boys Club;?",
                                       "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
    {"category": "General Knowledge", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy",
     "question": "When you cry in space, your tears stick to your face.", "correct_answer": "True",
     "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}, {"category": "Entertainment: Film", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy",
                                       "question": "In the original Star Wars trilogy, Alec Guinness provided the voice for Darth Vader.",
                                       "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]},
    {"category": "Entertainment: Japanese Anime & Manga", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy",
     "question": "The name of the attack ;Kamehameha; in Dragon Ball Z was named after a famous king of Hawaii.",
     "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
    {"category": "General Knowledge", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy",
     "question": "One of Donald Trumps 2016 Presidential Campaign promises was to build a border wall between the United States and Mexico.",
     "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
    {"category": "Science: Computers", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy",
     "question": "The Windows 7 operating system has six main editions.", "correct_answer": "True",
     "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}, {"category": "Mythology", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy",
                                       "question": "According to Greek Mythology, Atlas was an Olympian God.",
                                       "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]},
    {"category": "Entertainment: Video Games", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy",
     "question": "In Pok&eacute;mon, Bulbasaur is the only starter pokemon that is a Grass\/Poison type.",
     "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
    {"category": "Entertainment: Film", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy",
     "question": "George Lucas directed the entire original Star Wars trilogy.", "correct_answer": "False",
     "incorrect_answers": ["True"]}, {"category": "Entertainment: Board Games", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy",
                                      "question": ";PAYDAY: The Heist; is a sequel to the board game ;Payday;.",
                                      "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]},
    {"category": "Entertainment: Music", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy",
     "question": "Stevie Wonders real name is Stevland Hardaway Morris.", "correct_answer": "True",
     "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
    {"category": "Entertainment: Video Games", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy",
     "question": "In ;Undertale;, the main character of the game is Sans.", "correct_answer": "False",
     "incorrect_answers": ["True"]}, {"category": "Entertainment: Film", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy",
                                      "question": ";Minions; was released on the June 10th, 2015.",
                                      "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]},
    {"category": "Entertainment: Music", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy",
     "question": "Scatman Johns real name was John Paul Larkin.", "correct_answer": "True",
     "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
    {"category": "Entertainment: Video Games", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy",
     "question": "In Heroes of the Storm, the Cursed Hollow map gimmick requires players to kill the undead to curse the enemy team.",
     "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]},
    {"category": "Entertainment: Television", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy",
     "question": "In ;Star Trek;, Klingons are aliens.", "correct_answer": "True",
     "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
    {"category": "Entertainment: Video Games", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy",
     "question": ";Metal Gear Solid 3: Snake Eater; was released in 2004.", "correct_answer": "True",
     "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
    {"category": "Entertainment: Japanese Anime & Manga", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy",
     "question": "In the ;To Love-Ru; series, Golden Darkness is sent to kill Lala Deviluke.",
     "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]},
    {"category": "Entertainment: Video Games", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy",
     "question": "The ghosts in ;Pac-Man; and ;Ms. Pac-Man; have completely different behavior.",
     "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
    {"category": "Entertainment: Video Games", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy",
     "question": "The game ;Pocket Morty; has a Morty called ;Pocket Mortys Morty;?",
     "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
    {"category": "Entertainment: Video Games", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy",
     "question": ";Sonic the Hedgehog 2; originally was going to have a time travel system.",
     "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
    {"category": "History", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy",
     "question": "Thomas Crapper was a plumber who invented the flushing toilet.", "correct_answer": "False",
     "incorrect_answers": ["True"]}, {"category": "Entertainment: Video Games", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy",
                                      "question": "In the ;S.T.A.L.K.E.R.; series, the Freedom faction wishes to destroy the supernatural area known as  ;the Zone;.",
                                      "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]},
    {"category": "Entertainment: Video Games", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy",
     "question": "In ;Need for Speed: Porsche Unleashed;, the player can only drive cars manufactured by Porsche.",
     "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
    {"category": "Science & Nature", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy",
     "question": "Water always boils at 100&deg;C, 212&deg;F, 373.15K, no matter where you are.",
     "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]},
    {"category": "General Knowledge", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy",
     "question": "A pasodoble is a type of Italian pasta sauce.", "correct_answer": "False",
     "incorrect_answers": ["True"]}, {"category": "General Knowledge", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy",
                                      "question": "Slovakia is a member of European Union-", "correct_answer": "True",
                                      "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
    {"category": "Entertainment: Books", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy",
     "question": "The Harry Potter series of books, combined, are over 1,000,000 words in length.",
     "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}]
